{
    "id": "5162864d20dc4b9a943716629b432ab6",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Anybody who wants to ……………………. join the club.",
            "description": "We use can to express theoretical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1c62169f8f44e8bb131f95b09d193df"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… have won the race if I hadn’t fallen.",
            "description": "We can use could to talk about unrealized past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "could",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19d98cc19539439ebe84eb28464a1d77"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………….. go camping in June.",
            "description": "We do not use can to talk about future probability.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32c5b3ef43dd41a594a6ce1af4d66c24"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was so angry I …………………………. have slapped him.",
            "description": "We use could to talk about unrealized past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fe2755e18ae4018a276abc3b1770c1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "One day, it …………………………. be possible to travel to other planets.",
            "description": "\r\nWe use will be able to talk about future possibilities.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d42873f053884fb4839392a49b8cb6f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Chennai …………………………. be very warm throughout the year.",
            "description": "We often use can to talk about what is common or typical of a place.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "might",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "668a45c3e0e8428b971c7bf84a8fa050"
        },
        {
            "question": "War ………………………… break out any day.",
            "description": "We use can/could to talk about theoretical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0affc0940ff461bbecf390d542a2e13"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ……………………………. be at the door?",
            "description": "We use can in questions to talk about the logical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0549722254c4094a9ab9c65eb746948"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is Janet?’ ‘She …………………………. be at John’s place.’",
            "description": "Can is not used in affirmative clauses to talk about logical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7030de6e99fb45d9b97c732889207f25"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where ……………………….. we go?’",
            "description": "We use shall to ask for suggestions.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "369d36d65eaa4329a45fabca3a79718a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. see somebody coming.",
            "description": "To talk about seeing at a particular moment, we often use can see.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f07c7ce59c034396b1d354bb10d49f4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t help but wonder what we ………………………… do next.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "abec1e76cc0c4de2bd26e42eebcfa3be"
        }
    ]
}